trueandco.com 2019-07-23

# Read our Privacy Policy | True&Co.

The Effective Date of this policy is February 12, 2019

True&Co. operates the website located at www.trueandco.com. This Privacy Policy describes the information that is collected via our website and how that information is used. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@trueandco.com. This Privacy Policy also applies to services and products offered by True&Co., as well as any other applications, content or features that we may from time to time offer on our website.

##### Types of Information that True&Co collects

We collect two types of information from our website visitors: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. If you purchase our products or services, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form during the checkout process. We also request personally identifiable information from you during our online fit quiz in order to make the correct recommendations.

This contact information collected includes your name, email address, and shipping address, as well as the financial information you provide, such as a credit card number and its expiration date. We use the personally identifiable information for billing purposes and for order fulfillment. In the event we have an issue processing your order, we will use this information to contact you.

If you contact us via phone, email or through the feedback button on our website, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence. In any event, we will reserve the right to use your email address and any other personally identifiable information that you provide to us to respond to you, to make recommendations for your personal bra shop and to send you marketing materials for our own products and services.

If at any time you would like to change your personally identifiable information, no longer wish to receive materials from us or would like your personal information removed from our database, please contact us at support@trueandco.com. If you would like to unsubscribe, please use the "unsubscribe" function in all our email communications with you so that we know that you no longer wish to receive any materials from us.

##### Online tracking

Like most websites, our website may incorporate "pixel tags", or similar tracking technologies and "cookies" that allow us to track the actions of visitors of our website. Pixel tags and cookies are used to collect non-personally identifiable information, such as the name of your internet service provider, the IP address of the computer you are using, the type of browser software and operating system that is used, the date and time you access our website, the website address, if any, from which you linked directly to our website, the website address, if any, to which you travel from our website, your home page customization preferences and any other similar traffic-related information. We may also aggregate your information with similar data collected from other visitors to help us improve our website and the products, services, applications, content and features that we provide via our website.

We use our own cookies to help determine which of our ads are shown to you on other websites. To opt out of this targeted online advertising that utilizes our cookies, please [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

We also work with third-party companies that use their tracking technologies (including cookies and pixel tags) on our website in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These companies may collect information over time about your activity on our website and other sites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications and use this information to determine which ads you see on third-party websites and applications. These technologies and the information collected about you may also be used to track your activity across multiple devices. For more information about this practice and to understand your options including how to opt out of receiving these tailored advertisements, please visit http://www.aboutads.info.

Please note that even if you opt-out, these tracking technologies may still collect data and you will still see ads, but they will not be targeted based upon the information collected through these tracking technologies.

##### How the information we gather is used

We reserve the right to provide any information we collect, including personally identifiable information, to our employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to perform services on our behalf, including order fulfillment and website-related services such as web hosting, to improve website-related services and features, to perform maintenance services, and to distribute advertisements and other marketing materials on our behalf.

We also reserve the right to disclose any information that we collect to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any or all of the following reasons: (i) to comply with the law; (ii) to comply with legal processes or governmental requests; (iii) to prevent, investigate, detect, or prosecute criminal offenses or attacks on the technical integrity of our website or our network; and/or (iv) to protect the rights, property, safety and security of True&Co. and its employees, our website visitors, and/or the public.

Except as described in this Policy, we will not rent or sell information that directly identifies you, without your consent, to unrelated third parties, for their direct marketing purposes or otherwise, except as stated in this Privacy Policy. We may share your information with our parent company, our affiliates, and our business partners that sell our brands (e.g., Nordstrom, Hudson’s Bay, Target) for their own use, including for direct marketing purposes.

We (and our parent/affiliates) may share your information with our third party service providers that provide assistance with operating or hosting the website; providing or fulfilling the products and services you request; authorizing and processing of your payments; performing fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, marketing and promotional material distribution, website evaluation, data analysis, website improvements, and, where applicable, data cleansing, marketing, promotions and other services performed on our behalf.

Some parts of the website may contain embedded content controlled by third parties (e.g., social media) for services such as social sharing, commenting and displaying video or images. When you interact with these services, they may collect information from and about you and your interaction with their content, including the URL of the web page you are visiting. This activity will be subject to the privacy policy of and your settings for the third party network or service. Please be aware that they may track your activity, including through the use of cookies or similar technology, without you needing to interact with them.

In addition, we may share or transfer information about you to unrelated third parties:

  * when you engage in activities that are sponsored by third parties (e.g., cobranded offerings);
  * for online analytics purposes (e.g., with Google Analytics);
  * if required to do so by law or to comply with a legal requirement, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process;
  * to investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; or
  * when we believe it is necessary to protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety.

We may use or share information that does not reasonably identify you with any third party and for any purpose.

##### We are Committed to Making Sure Your Information is Protected

Our physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards meet or exceed current federal standards regarding the protection of customer information. We also require contractors and outside companies who work with us to adhere to strict privacy standards through their contractual agreements with us. Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and our servers, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the website. Any information that you provide to us is done so entirely at your own risk.

##### We Reserve the Right to Update and Revise this Privacy Policy at Any Time

From time to time we review this Privacy Policy to ensure that it complies with applicable law. Consequently, we reserve the right to update and revise this Privacy Policy at any time. You will know if this Privacy Policy has been revised since your last visit to the website by referring to the "Effective Date of Current Policy" date at the top of this page. Your use of our website constitutes your acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy as amended or revised by us from time to time, and you should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of its terms.

##### Business Partnerships and data transfer

If we sell all or any part of our business, or sell or transfer all or a material part of our assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or other transfer or disposition of any part our business, we reserve the right to access, transfer or disclose any and all information that we collect from our website's visitors, or that we otherwise collect in connection with the website, to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

##### Our Website may Contain Links to Other Websites.

Please be aware that we are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any websites that you access through our website and that this Privacy Policy applies solely to the information which we collect through our website. We encourage you to ensure that you read the privacy statements of all the destination websites which you visit.

For questions about this policy, or how we use your data, please contact support@trueandco.com.
